《勇敢者的游戏》
(1869年)
别怕 一群狼而已 加油干 咱们就要成功了
Don't worry, it's a pack of wolves. Come on, we're almost rid of it.
- 凯勒布 它在追我 - 赶紧爬上来
- Caleb, it's after me! - Grab on!
快闪
Run! Run!
回来 本杰明 一定要把这祸害埋了
No, Benjamin, we have to finish this.
发什么愣 快动手
Come on, help me bury it.
要是某人把它又挖出来呢
What if someone digs it up?
只能祈求上帝保佑了
May God have mercy on his soul.
(布兰福特特 1英里)
(新罕布什尔州 布兰福特镇 1969年)
- 嗨 艾伦 - 嗨 迈克鲁德小姐
- Hi, Alan. - Hi, Miss Magruder.
- 下午好 艾伦 - 好啊 弗兰克
- Afternoon, Alan. - Hey, Frank.
- 可以过了 艾伦 - 谢了 比尔
- All yours, Alan. - Thanks, Bill.
扁他
Get him!
姓巴的 要你好看
Prepare to die, Parrish!
姓巴的 你急什么
Parrish, what's the rush?
他要去鞋厂
He's going to the factory!
滚阿 夹尾巴的
Go on, Parrish!
去找你爹地
Run to Daddy.
有种别出来
We'll be waiting.
卡尔
Hi, Carl.
艾伦老弟
Hey, Alan, my man.
过来看这个
I gotta show you something. Come here.
我研究了快一年
I've been working on this all year.
我约好下午见你父亲
I got an appointment with your father...
要给他看...这个 你瞧瞧
...to show him this. Go ahead, take it.
如何
What do you think?
你想他会喜欢吗
Think he'll like it?
这是什么
What is it?
老弟 这是未来
What is it? This is the future.
如果张伯伦穿这鞋
If Wilt Chamberlain will wear them...
全国百姓都会抢着买
...there'll be a pair of those in every closet in America.
一定大大的流行
That will be the height of fashion.
怎么啦
What's wrong?
- 没什么 - 艾伦
- Nothing. - Alan!
你来干嘛
What are you doing?
我说过 工厂不是游乐园 很危险的
This factory isn't a playground. It's dangerous.
我想搭你的便车
Can I have a ride home?
比利又来惹你了
Is Billy Jessup picking on you again?
你迟早要面对他
Son, you're gonna have to face him sooner or later.
不管怕什么事 都要勇敢的面对
If you're afraid of something, you've got to stand and face it.
去吧
Now, run on, son.
你知道他不该来的
You know better than to let the boy play here.
抱歉 老板
Sorry, sir.
你要我看什么
What was it you wanted to show me?
我马上拿来
Just a minute, sir.
怎么搞成这样
What the devil...
谁干的好事
Who did this?
说啊
Well?
是我
I did, sir.
别以为你姓巴就可以钓我的马子
Being a Parrish doesn't mean you can hang around with my girl.
我们只是朋友
We're just friends.
到此为止
Not anymore.
扁他
Get him!
抢他的单车
I've got his bike!
混蛋
Jerks!
好棒
Neat.
艾伦
Alan?
是你吗
Are you home?
宝贝 怎么又被扁了
Alan, not again. Come on.
勤奋 毅力 乐观...
Hard work, determination, cheerful outlook...
这都是本镇居民的特质
...attributes that exemplify Brantford spirit...
创建以来始终如此
...since our forefathers first settled this town.
尽管此地气候严酷
Despite the harshness of our native clime
土壤坚硬无比 我们却能...
and the granite of our soil...we have...
欣欣向荣
Prospered.
- 早上明明记得的 - 今晚你也会记得
- I knew it all this morning. - You'll know it all tonight.
走吧
Right. Let's go.
山姆 我们得跟亚伦谈谈
Sam, we have to talk to Alan.
我们要走了
Well, we're on our way.
我跟你父亲说了...
I told your father what you told me,
对方不只比利一个
that it wasn't just Billy Jessup.
我要是知道...
If I'd known that,
- 就不会... - 没关系 老爹
- I wouldn't have... - It's okay, Dad.
不过 你要知道 我很以你为荣
But I want you to know that I'm proud of you.
对方人多 你也不怕
You faced them, even though you were outnumbered.
既然你像个男子汉 因此我们决定...
Since you took it like a man, your mother and I have decided...
送你去念克利福塞男校
...that you're ready to go to The Cliffside School for Boys.
恭喜我们的宝贝
Congratulations, sweetheart.
你们不要我住在家里
You don't want me living here anymore?
我们原本就有这想法
It's always been the plan that you go to Cliffside.
咱们巴家的人从18世纪开始就念的这所学校
I mean, Parrishes have been going to Cliffside ever since the 1700s.
包括你叔叔史凯勒
Even your Uncle Skylar went there.
看看这个
Look at this.
"巴里斯馆"
Parrish Hall?
那是学校宿舍
It's the main dormitory.
好极了 就因为我姓巴 他们才来找茬
This is great. Kids are on my case here because I'm a Parrish.
还叫我去住...
Just wait till
巴氏纪念宿舍
I'm living in a building named after me.
是纪念我父亲的
It was named after my father.
好 那你去住啊
Good. Why don't you live in it?
我住过了
I did.
没有那些岁月 就没有今天的我
I wouldn't be who I am if it weren't for my years there.
也许我不想跟你一样
Maybe I don't want to be who you are.
甚至不想当巴家的人
Maybe I don't even want to be a Parrish.
你不够格 言行得像个样 去拿外套
You won't be, not till you start acting like one.Get your coat.
学校的事也免谈咯
I guess I'm not ready for Cliffside, then.
下周日就去 不准再和我提这件事
We're taking you there next Sunday. I don't want to hear any other word about it!
你休想
You won't!
我再也不跟你讲话了
I'm never talking to you again!
- 山姆 - 别提了
- Sam... - Don't.
- 山姆 - 干嘛
- Sam. - What?
没什么
Nothing.
你怎么来了
Why are you here?
我把你的车送回来
I brought your bike.
没必要的
You didn't have to.
我自己会去找比利算账
I was going to Billy's to get it myself.
我叫比利别再烦你
I told Billy to stop picking on you.
你是白费唇舌 我们改天再谈
You wasted your breath. We'll talk about it some other time.
什么声音
What was that?
你也听见了
You heard it too?
当然啊
Of course I heard it.
这边走
Come on
- 我发现一个好怪的棋盘游戏 - 棋盘游戏
- I found this really weird game in the factory. - A game?
魔幻棋
Jumanji.
"这个游戏为你设计 如果你想遗世独立
"A game for those who seek to find a way to leave their world behind.
丢骰子看走几步 掷出一对可继续
You roll the dice to move your token. Doubles gets another turn.
谁先抵终点谁获胜" 要不要玩
The first to reach the end wins." You want to play?
学前班的小孩才玩这个
I quit playing board games five years ago.
莎拉
Sarah!
一定是磁力或是什么作用
It's gotta be magnetized or something.
艾伦 你看
Alan, look.
"这种飞虫 昼伏夜出"
"At night they fly,
"快快逃命"
you better run.
"自求多福"
These winged things are not much fun."
什么声音
What was that?
不知道
I don't know.
- 快拿走 - 好
- Put it away, Alan. - Okay.
糟糕...
Oh, no.
它以为我掷了骰子
The game thinks I rolled.
"它以为" 是什么意思
What do you mean, "the game thinks"?
"快到丛林孵豆芽"
"In the jungle you must wait...
"直到出现五或八"
...until the dice read five or eight."
"快到丛林孵豆芽"
In the jungle you must wait?
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
(二十六年后)
镇上确实需要个小客栈
A bed and breakfast is just what this town needs.
机会实在难得 何况还附家具
It was pretty hard to pass up. Especially full of furniture.
我忘了这屋子应该这么大
I keep forgetting how big this place is.
朱蒂 彼德 快来看
Judy, Peter, come look at this.
柜台可以设在这里
I'm gonna put a reception area right over here.
这里是大厅 酒吧
And a bar over here in the parlour.
听起来很棒
That sounds lovely.
你跟孩子们一定会很开心
I'm sure you and your kids will be very happy here.
实际上 他们是我的侄子
Actually, they're my late brother's.
我兄嫂去年冬天死翘翘了
He and his wife passed away just last winter.
这里很棒吧
Is this something, or what?
的确
It sure is.
你觉得如何 够不够大
What do you think? Is it big enough for you?
悲剧发生后...彼德就不说话了
Peter hasn't spoken a word since it happened.
我的天...
Oh, my.
真是抱歉 太不幸了
I'm so sorry. How terribly awful.
没关系
It's okay.
我们跟父母也不熟
We barely even knew our parents.
他们常年在外...
They were always away...
不是在瑞士滑雪 在摩纳哥赌钱...
Skiing in St. Moritz, gambling in Monte Carlo...
就是在非洲狩猎
...safariing in darkest Africa.
也不知爱不爱我们
We didn't even know if they loved us.
但他们的游艇沉没时...
But when the sheik's yacht went down...
他们写了一封诀别书
...they managed to write a beautiful goodbye note...
塞在香槟酒瓶里在海上被人发现
...that was found floating in a champagne bottle amongst the debris.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我兄嫂很顾家
They were very devoted parents.
在加拿大出了车祸
It was a car crash in Canada.
契约就寄给我吧
You'll send me the escrow papers?
明天一早
First thing tomorrow.
得去找锁匠来
I'll have to get a locksmith for this one.
彼德 玩具收起来
Peter, pick up your toys, please.
彼德 皮箱放进阁楼
Peter, take this suitcase up to the attic.
然后来吃冰淇淋
Then we can all have ice cream.
我来杯酒
And bourbon.
怎么啦
What? What is it?
我要去住汽车旅馆
I'm going to Motel 6.
拜托
Oh, for heaven's sake.
没看见蝙蝠屎
I don't see any guano.
他说像这个
He said it looked like that.
这是非洲蝙蝠
That's an African bat.
有人说在60年代看过
Some kid said she saw some back in the '60s...
新英格兰哪里会有
...but we don't get bats like that in New England.
他明明看到了
That's what he saw.
不管是什么...反正已经没了
Well, whatever it was, it's gone now.
这房子 我倒不担心蝙蝠
Bats aren't what I'd worry about in this house, anyways.
那你担心什么
What would you worry about?
就我个人来说
Well, personally...
我可不住发生过凶案的房子
...I wouldn't want to live where someone was murdered.
- 凶案 - 对头
- Murdered? - Yep.
艾伦·巴里斯 我猜是他父亲杀的
Little Alan Parrish. I say his father did it.
这房子要藏尸体 容易得很
There's 1001 places he could've hid the body in this house.
特别是分尸之后
Especially if he chopped it up first.
喂 上面的
Hey up there!
头一天上学 别迟到了
You don't want to be late for your first day of school.
半只蝙蝠也没有
Not a bat in sight, ma'am.
听到没
Hear that?
这房子没什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of in this house.
你们刚上学... 校长就要请家长
I can't believe I have to see your principal after your first day.
如何是好
What am I gonna do?
我们先吃完晚饭...
Let's try to relax and finish dinner.
聊些别的事
Talk about something else.
难怪这房子那么便宜
We know why you got the house cheap.
26年前 一个叫艾伦·巴里斯的男孩住在这里
Twenty-six years ago, a kid named Alan Parrish lived here.
有一天 他突然失踪
One day he just disappeared.
他父母把他分尸藏在墙壁里
His parents chopped him up and hid him in the walls.
够了 老是编谎话 罚你禁足
That's it. I'm sick and tired of your lies. You're grounded.
无所谓 反正这鸟镇没处去
Fine, there's nowhere to go in this stupid town anyway.
让你知道一下...
Just for your information,
我可没说谎
that wasn't a lie.
有没有听见什么
Did you hear anything a little wild?
你想不想爸妈
Do you miss Mom and Dad?
不想
No.
骗人
Liar.
你再继续编谎话 会被送去看心理医生
Cut that out, or they'll send you to a shrink.
你不讲话 问题才大呢
Where are they gonna send you if you don't start talking?
如果有耽搁 我会打电话
If I get held up at the permit office, I'll give you call.
校车马上就到了
The school bus will be here any minute.
钥匙拿了没
You guys still have your house keys?
我的话听到没有
You guys listening to me?
喂
Hello?
- 喂 - 怎么
- Hello? - What?
我陪你们等车好了
Maybe I should wait till the bus comes.
你父母会送你们上车吗
Did your parents used to put you on the bus?
不会
No.
确定吗
Are you sure?
我可以送你们去
I could drop you off.
没关系 校车马上就到了
No, don't worry about us. The bus will be here any minute.
今天拜托乖一点
Okay. Please be good today.
你听见了
You do hear it.
听见什么
Hear what?
从哪里传来的
Where is it coming from?
拿过来
Let's bring it over here.
奇怪 粘住了
Weird. They're stuck.
"这个游戏为你设计 如果你想遗世独立
"Jumanji, a game for those who seek to leave their worlds behind.
丢骰子决定走几步 掷出一对可以继续
Roll the dice to move. Doubles get another turn.
谁先抵终点谁获胜"
The first player to reach the end wins."
一定是装了微晶片
It's gotta be microchips or something.
你先玩
You go first.
六点
Six.
"只要轻轻叮一下 包你浑身都发麻"
"A tiny bite can make you itch, make you sneeze, make you twitch."
不要
Don't!
"达成任务难上难"
"This will not be an easy mission.
"成群泼猴来阻拦"
Monkeys slow the expedition."
什么声音
What is that?
猴子是游戏带来的
I bet those monkeys came from the game.
蚊子也是
The mosquitoes too.
糟糕 我没看见这个
I didn't see this part.
"冒险家注意..."
"Adventurers, beware."
"Adventurers, beware.
"游戏一开启 就得玩到底"
Do not begin unless you intend to finish.
"游戏的风风雨雨 要它们如数散去"
The consequences of the game vanish when a player has reached Jumanji...
"得有人硬撑到底"
...and called out its name."
- 猴子跑了 - 好
- The monkeys are gone. - Good.
- 把它丢了 - 等一下
- Put it away. - Wait!
它说玩到底 就没事了
If we finish the game, it'll all go away.
就这么办 否则姑姑会气疯
Let's do it or Aunt Nora'll pitch a fit.
我们得玩快点 反正不用技巧
We should get through it quickly. I mean, there's no skill involved.
不 你掷出一对
No, you rolled doubles.
可以继续 掷啊
You get another turn. Roll!
五点
Five.
"利齿巨虫"
"His fangs are sharp.
"爱吃人"
He likes your taste.
"快快闪避"
Your party better move
"免遗恨"
posthaste."
听起来怪恐怖的
I don't like the sound of that.
有人来了
Someone's in here.
这是假的 彼德
It's not real, Peter.
是我们的幻觉
It's a hallucination.
快闪
Run, Peter!
我回来了...
I'm back.
小单车
My bike.
谁掷了五或八
Somebody roll a five or an eight?
是他
He did.
救星 救星
Thank you! Thank you!
对不起 吓到你了...
Sorry if I scared you.
我回来了
I'm back!
老爹 老妈
Mom! Dad!
我到家了
I'm home!
我回来了
I'm back!
是我
It's me!
是艾伦 爸爸 妈妈
It's me, Alan, Mom and Dad!
我到家了
I'm home!
我回来了
I'm back!
你是不是妹妹
Are you my little sister?
我是朱蒂 他是彼德
No, I'm Judy and he's Peter.
妈呢 爸在鞋厂吗
Where's Mom? Is Dad at the factory?
你是不是...
Are you...
艾伦·巴里斯
...Alan Parrish?
对
Yeah.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我们现在住在这里
We live here now.
我爸妈呢
Where's my mom and dad?
不知道
We don't know.
这房子空了好多年
This house has been empty for years.
大家以为你死了
Everyone thought you were dead.
对不起
Sorry.
- 再说一遍 - 我说"红毛 长尾"
- Give me that description again. - Red fur and tails.
请你给我下车 到人行道上
Get down off of my car, please, and get up on the sidewalk.
请问今年是哪一年
What year is it?
这是最新一年的车
It was brand-new.
- 今年是哪一年 - 1995 你忘啦
- No. What year is it? - 1995, remember?
有没有证件
You got some I.D.?
在你的泰山装口袋里
Let me guess, it's in your other Tarzan outfit.
26年了
26 years.
你住这一带吗
Are you from around here?
本是的
I was.
后来被魔幻棋吸走了
But I've been in Jumanji.
印度尼西亚
Indonesia.
他参加和平工作团
He was in the Peace Corps.
班特利...
Bentley...
- 是卡尔·班特利 - 他是你亲戚吗
- Carl Bentley, the sole man. - Is this man related to you?
他是我...姑丈
Yes, he's our uncle.
他常这样打扮
Does he always dress like that?
是啊 他是素食主义者
Yeah, he's a vegetarian.
走开
Get out of there!
猴子...
Monkeys. Monkeys.
他没少根筋吧
Is he all right upstairs?
他前阵子头受过伤
He suffered a head injury a few months ago.
你别走
Don't you move!
站住
Stop!
跑死你娃
Don't move, don't move.
你要去哪里
Wait! Where are you going?
去找我父母
To find my parents!
走
Come on.
等一下
Wait!
我爸爸以前在这里制鞋
My dad used to make shoes here.
新英格兰最好的鞋
They were the best shoes in New England.
对不起
Sorry.
没事 别紧张
Easy, girl.
这鞋厂怎么啦
Do you know what happened to the shoe factory?
关掉了
Yeah, it folded up.
跟镇上其他店家一样
Like everything else in this town.
外头冷 来杯咖啡吧
It's pretty cold out there. How about some coffee?
巴氏鞋厂为什么关掉
Why would they close Parrish Shoes?
山姆的孩子失踪后
When his kid ran away, Sam
他尽一切能力去寻找 所有的时间 金钱
put everything he had into finding him.His time, his money...
全部投入
Everything.
过了一阵子 他就不来工厂了
After a while, he stopped coming to work.
什么都不在乎了
He just quit caring.
没有人像他那样爱孩子
I don't think anybody loved his boy more than Sam did.
拿着
Here.
你会冻坏的
You're gonna freeze out there.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们夫妇还在吗
Are the Parrishes still around?
我不时去看他们
I see them now and then.
他们住在亚当斯街
They're over on Adams Street.
我们父母也不在了
Our parents are dead too.
他们是在中东斡旋时...
They were in the Middle East negotiating peace when...
我爸爸在广告界
Our dad was in advertising.
你一定很想他
I bet you miss him, huh?
我也是
Me too.
他又要走了
There he goes again.
我说 尽管你现在很失落 不过咱们得完成游戏
Listen I know you're upset, but we should finish the game.
我们 何必找我
We? Why do you need me?
万一出现可怕的东西
Just in case any other scary stuff comes out.
我姑姑房里有狮子 我怎么办
Plus there's a lion in my aunt's room.
你当我是马戏团的
Do I look like a Ringling Brother?
她快回家了
She'll be home soon.
吓她一大跳 希望她不怕猫
Won't she be surprised? I hope she's not allergic to cats.
要拿担架 来帮忙
Larry, we need the wheels. Give me a hand.
- 撞得厉害吗 - 不 是被怪虫叮的
- Did we hit her hard? - No, it looks like another weird bite.
- 果然没错 - 已经五十多个了
- Yeah, it's another one. - That's over 50.
怎么一回事
What's going on?
轻一点
Easy now, easy.
- 看 那不是汤马斯太太吗 - 谁呀
- Isn't that Mrs. Thomas? - Who's that?
- 中介公司那个 - 安静
- The realtor. - Quiet.
听
Listen.
听见没
You hear that?
听见什么
Hear what?
上车
Get in the car.
想想看
Okay, think.
什么东西比我先出来
What came out of the game before me?
狮子 一群猴子 还有...
There was a lion, a bunch of monkeys and...
那个
That!
没事...只是个虫子
It's okay, it's okay. It's just a bug.
这里很安全
We're safe in here.
看到没没问题
See we're fine.
只要坐低一点 就叮不到
If we stay low, he can't get through there too far.
别担心 没问题
Don't you worry. We're fine.
它进不来 有玻璃挡住
He can't get through the glass.
我们很安全
We're safe.
你们会开车吗
Do you know how to drive?
不会 小意思
No? That's no problem.
我爹曾让我倒车到汽车道上
My dad used to let me back the car down the driveway.
有一次经验
Once.
没什么难的
So, what's the big deal?
上路了
Here we go!
等一等
Wait a minute.
车顶
The top!
小事一桩
Piece of cake.
艾伦
Alan.
不要拿那玩意靠近我
Keep that thing away from me!
你何时才要玩 我姑姑就快回来了
When are you gonna help us play? Our aunt will be home soon.
好 你就告诉她 她已被扫地出门
Good. You can inform her that she's the ex-owner of this house.
我父母既然不在 我就是这里的主人了
I hope you realize with my parents gone, this home belongs to me.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank you.
不必用香蕉叶子了
No more banana leaves.
那些猴子会破坏生态环境
What do you think those monkeys will do to the ecosystem?
你们坐好 听我说命运的故事吧
Just sit right back And you'll hear a tale of a fateful trip
他们乘坐小船从热带港口出发
That started out in this tropic port aboard this tiny ship
强壮的水手 勇敢的船长...
The mate was a mighty sailing man. The skipper brave and sure
5个乘客出海 34小时的旅游
Five passengers set sail that day. For a three-hour tour
你怎么啦
What happened to you?
用玻璃刮脸吗
Did you shave with a piece of glass?
你又怎么了 输了钱回家啦
What happened to you? Did the Clampetts have a yard sale?
这辈子第一次刮胡子
I've never shaved before.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我跟彼德玩 你看着就好
How about Peter and I play, and you just sort of watch?
谢谢 我看过了
Thanks, I've seen it.
你不帮忙 那要干嘛
If you won't help us, what are you gonna do?
不知道
I don't know.
继续过我的日子吧
Pretty much take up where I left off.
看倪老师是否还教六年级
I wonder if Mrs. Niedermeyer's still teaching sixth grade.
算了 他不会帮忙的 他怕了
Come on, he's not gonna help us. He's afraid.
你说什么
What did you say?
你害怕
You're afraid.
怕成乌龟了
It's okay to be afraid.
我们去客厅玩
Let's set it up in the living room.
你们不知道这玩意的厉害
You have no idea what you're getting yourself into.
好坏我们会自己应付 不用你帮忙
Whatever it is, we can handle it. We don't need your help.
我不同意
I don't think so.
你们以为猴子 蚊子
You think monkeys, mosquitoes
还有狮子很凶
and lions are bad?
这才刚开始
That's just the beginning.
我见过的东西 你们做恶梦时才会出现
I've seen things you've only seen in your nightmares.
连想都想不到的
Things you can't even imagine.
看也看不见
Things you can't even see.
有些东西每晚来找你
There are things that hunt you in the night.
有些不停尖叫
Then something screams.
你听见他们在吃东西
Then you hear them eating.
就祈祷你别变成甜点
And you hope to God that you're not dessert.
害怕
Afraid?
你们还不知道何谓害怕
You don't even know what afraid is.
没有我 你们活不到五分钟
You will not last five minutes without me.
这么说...
So...
欢迎你的加入
you're gonna help us?
我看你们玩...
I'll watch...
我不怕
...but I'm not afraid.
彼德 你刚才好酷
Peter, that was very cool.
这叫激将法 爸爸常用来对付我
It's reverse psychology. Dad used to pull it on me all the time.
准备好没
Ready?
艾伦好了没
Alan, ready?
你没法准备的
There is no "ready".
我再试一次
I'll try it again.
艾伦 没动静
Alan, it's not working.
糟了 不是轮到你
It's not your turn.
是啊我先掷 然后彼德 掷两次 现在又该我了
I rolled first. Then Peter twice because he got doubles.
现在又该我了
Now it's my turn again.
看
No, look.
两个棋子是你们的
Two of the pieces are yours, right?
另两个是谁的
Who's the other pieces?
大象是我的
The elephant was mine.
69年开始的那盘还没完
You're playing the game I started in 1969.
我要玩才行
I'm gonna have to play.
不该我
It's not my turn.
那该谁呢
Whose turn is it?
莎拉·惠特尔
Sarah Whittle.
她以前住这地方
This is where she used to live.
她住鬼屋阿
This place gives me the creeps.
我们常在阳台上玩
We used to play on this porch.
(通灵大师 丝灵娜夫人)
她一定不住这里 可能跟比利都结婚了
She doesn't live here. She probably married Billy Jessup.
- 来都来了 - 不妨打听一下
- Come on. - Let's at least ask.
- 说不定她知道 - 当然 她能通灵嘛
- Maybe she'll know where Sarah went. - She'll know. She's a psychic.
有道理
Good point.
以前阳台比较大
I remember the porch being a lot bigger.
帮个忙好吗
Can you help us?
有没有预约
Do you have an appointment?
没有 我们在找个人
No, we're trying to find someone.
丝灵娜夫人在忙
Madam Serena can't see anyone now.
或许你能帮忙
Maybe you can help us.
什么事
What is it?
我找个人 以前住这儿的
We're looking for someone who used to live here.
我一直住这里
No, I've lived here my whole life.
那你一定认识莎拉·惠特尔
Then you must know Sarah Whittle.
你们找她干嘛
What do you want with Sarah Whittle?
莎拉
Sarah?
我已经改名了
I don't go by that name anymore.
莎拉·惠特尔
Sarah Whittle?
你要做什么
What do you want?
26年前 你跟邻居一个男孩玩个游戏
Twenty-six years ago, you played a game with a little boy down the street.
有鼓声的游戏...
A game with drums.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我就是那个男孩
I was that little boy, Sarah.
艾伦
Alan?
你害死她了
You killed her.
请留言 大夫会尽快回话
Leave a message and the doctor will call you back at his earliest convenience.
鲍大夫...
Dr. Boorstein,
我是莎拉·惠特尔 请尽快给我回话
it's Sarah Whittle. Please call me as soon as you can.
我的药剂量需要检查
I think I need to have my dosage checked.
我们常谈的那件事... 你说并未发生的那件
That event we've been discussing, the one that didn't really happen?
今天我碰到那个...并未失踪的男孩
I'm having an episode here with the boy who didn't really disappear.
我在他家客厅 喝柠檬汁
I'm sitting in his living room, drinking lemonade.
请回电话
If you could call me,
我很想听听你的解释
I'd really be interested in your interpretation.
- 他一会就会打来 - 反正也是闲着...
- He'll call me back. - While we're waiting...
- 妈呀！不不不！ - 莎拉
- God! No, no, no! - Sarah.
我心理治疗好久 才相信没发生过这诡异的事情
I've spent 2000 hours in therapy convincing myself that didn't exist.
我认为是我在幻想
What happened to you was so awful. I made it up.
的确很可怕...
It was awful. It was awful.
没错
It really was.
但那是真的
But it was real.
不对 你父亲把你杀了 还把你剁碎
No, it wasn't real. Your father murdered you and chopped you up.
莎拉 别胡说
Sarah, come on!
我父亲会那么做?
My dad did that?
我父亲难得抱我
My father could barely hug me...
更别提把我剁碎
...let alone cut me into little pieces.
26年前
Twenty-six years ago,
我们开始了一场游戏
we started playing a little game.
现在...
And now...
我们要坐下来
...we're all gonna sit down
把游戏玩完
and we're gonna finish it.
你猜怎样
And guess what?
该你了
It's your turn.
掷吧
Play the game.
- 不 不 - 好
- Oh, no, no. - Fine.
骰子给我 回家去吧
Just give me the dice and you can go home.
不玩没关系
You don't have to play.
艾伦 你人太好了
Thank you, Alan.
骗子
Oh, my God!
你怎么这样
How could you do that?
这叫丛林法则
It's the law of the jungle.
慢慢就习惯了
You'll get used to it.
我还一直当你是个善鬼
When I think of the energy I spent visualizing you as a radiant spirit...
快念吧
Go on, read it.
"此物生长快过春笋"
"They grow much faster than bamboo.
"不想被捉步步留神"
Take care or they'll come after you."
好极了
Oh, great!
告诉我 这只是幻觉
Oh, God. Tell me this isn't happening.
可惜不是
It is.
别靠近墙壁 别碰其他东西
Stay away from the walls. Don't touch anything.
别做大动作
No quick movements.
- 好漂亮 - 可不是吗
- They're beautiful. - Yeah, they're beautiful.
别碰紫色的 它会射出毒刺
Don't touch the purple ones. They shoot poisonous barbs.
尤其要远离又大又黄的花苞
And definitely stay away from the pods. The big yellow ones.
什么又大又黄
What big yellow ones?
捉住了
I got you! Get his arms!
把它扯掉
Get it off me! Get it off me!
我的天
Oh, my God!
抓紧
Hang on.
我马上来
Got him? I'll be right back.
爷爷失礼了
Sorry, Angus.
收割时刻
Harvest time!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我的天
Oh, my God!
我的车...
My car.
我的车
Oh, my car.
请回答...
Carl please...
有谁看见卡尔了
Dose anybody see Carl?
有这种事
I can't believe this.
拜托 发动...
Start, start, please. Yes!
- 卡尔 请回答 - 我是卡尔
- Carl? Come in, Carl. - Carl here.
你死哪去了 好多动物到处乱窜
Where have you been? We've got an animal control situation.
叫史丹和威利去
Get Stan and Willy on it.
我要去姓巴的老家看看
I've gotta check out a suspicious character at the Parrish place.
我该进消防队才对
I should've been a fireman.
莎拉
Sarah!
放开我
Get your hands off me!
游戏还没完呢
The game is not over yet.
对我来说完了
It is for me.
这里不是丛林
You are not in the jungle anymore.
住手 不能这样对我
Stop this! You don't treat people like this.
有谁要冰茶我来泡茶
Anybody up for iced tea? I'm gonna make some tea.
拜托 上次我玩了下 一辈子就毁了
Alan please, last time I played this game it ruined my life.
你的一辈子毁了
It ruined your life?
"快到丛林孵豆芽"
"In the jungle you must wait
"直到出现五或八"
till the dice read five or eight."
我当时是个小女孩
I was a little girl, Alan.
你不见了
You disappeared.
一群蝙蝠...
And a bunch of bats
包围着我 追着我到马路上
surrounded me and chased me down the street.
我当时害怕
I was afraid.
对不起 艾伦
I'm sorry, Alan.
没人相信我 我好孤单
No one believed me. I was alone.
莎拉 我也是 转眼26年
So was I, for 26 years, Sarah.
我也是
Me too.
没关系 莎拉 我们也害怕
It's okay, Sarah. We're scared too.
只要玩完 这些就会消失
But if we finish the game, it'll all go away.
万一我被困住呢
What if I get stuck in the game?
不会的
You won't.
因为我会玩下去
Because I won't stop playing.
我也不会
And neither will I.
I won't either.
来吧 莎拉
Come on, Sarah.
拜托
Please?
就知道今天日子不好
I knew this was gonna be a bad day.
来吧
Come on,
没事的
we'll be fine.
只要保持冷静
We just have to keep our heads.
没什么大不了的
And roll with the punches.
"蛮荒僻野"
"A hunter from
"一猎神"
the darkest wild...
"鲁莽射击不留人"
...makes you feel just like a child."
什么意思
What is it?
范培特...
Van Pelt.
没用的孬种 回来跟我决斗
You miserable coward! Come back and face me like a man.
准头不够
Not good enough, Sonny Jim.
看你往哪跑
Coming, ready or not.
喂 听着
Hey, you!
枪扔掉 手举高
Drop your gun and get your hands in the air!
有这种事
Man, I don't believe this!
即使艾伦平安无事
Even if Alan gets out of this situation...
事情也会不断重演
...it'll happen over and over again.
人长期压抑怒气
When you carry repressed anger,
吸收了许多负能量 就会出事
it attracts a lot of negative energy.
例如陷身丛林
Things happen, like ending up in the jungle. That was no accident.
这不是没道理的
There are no accidents.
该谁了
Whose turn is it?
该我
It's my turn.
好极了 继续
Really? Great.
你应该讲明有这号人物
You might've told us there was a man who hunts people.
我哪知道 骰子掷了才晓得
I didn't know. It's just a roll of the dice.
因为这个 你才不想玩
Is he the reason you didn't want to play?
你本来也不想玩
You didn't want to play, either?
还说什么 游戏开始了 就得结束
Mr. We started 26 years ago and now we gotta finish it?
你跟他有何瓜葛
What's with this guy?
他是猎人 以打猎为业 现在他要捕杀我
He's a hunter. He kills things. Right now, he wants to kill me.
- 为何找上你 - 为何找上我
- Why you? - Why me?
不知道 也许他讨厌我的样子
I don't know. You'd think it'd be a waste of his time.
或是他想装饰墙壁
Maybe I'd look good on his wall.
该你了
It's your turn.
你们不能沟通一下吗
Have you ever talked with him about your differences?
你疯啦 他拿着枪...
Are you crazy? The man has a gun...
不准说我疯
Don't ever call me crazy Alan.
永远不准
Ever.
我说出你给棋盘吸走了 大家都说我疯了
Everyone's called me crazy ever since I said you were sucked into a game.
我来继续掷
Maybe I should roll.
赞成
Yeah.
大家当我是凶案的目击者
I was the girl who saw you murdered.
我14岁生日没人来参加派对
Did anyone come to my 14 birthday party?
我要掷了
Hello, I'm rolling now.
- 什么比利 - 我掷了
- Billy who? - I am gonna roll.
怎么忘啦
Are you an owl?
拜托 丝灵娜女士 挖挖你的潜意识
Come on, Madam Serena,dig into your consciousness.
掷吧
Here, just roll.
找出你的老相好比利
Find the memory of your old boyfriend Billy.
抢你单车那个
The kid who'd steal your bicycle?
带你去看电影那个
The kid who took you to the movies.
"听个清楚 不是打雷 按兵不动 可要倒霉"
"Don't be fooled, it isn't thunder. Staying put would be a blunder."
- 你早熟 - 你才早熟
- You're immature. - You are!
你肯定是的 至于我
I know you are, but what am I?
有没有感觉到
Do you feel that?
仔细听
Listen.
快跑
Run!
动物惊群了
It's a stampede!
游戏带着
The game!
别回头看
Don't look back!
不要
Not the game!
你干嘛不拿好
Why didn't you grab the game, Peter?
别理他 他是天秤座的
Ignore him. He's a Libra.
- 他要去哪 - 它会去水边
- Where are you going? - He'll head for water!
走吧
Let's go.
我是你阿姨 你跑哪去了
It's Aunt Nora. Where have you been?
抱歉 你拨错号了
I'm sorry, dear. You have the wrong number.
等等我
Wait for me!
- 要买什么 - 我要这种子弹
- What can I do for you? - I'll have a gross of these.
这种1903年就停产了
They stopped making these in 1903.
可恶
Damn.
只好连枪也换了
Then I shall need a replacement weapon.
要等一段日子
There's a waiting period.
还得先填申请表
And you'll have to fill out these.
我可以代填
Or I could fill these out.
路易斯
Louise.
要是有人问起...
Now, anyone asks,
别说在这儿买的
you didn't get this here.
你是邮差吗
You're not a postal worker, are you?
艾伦
Alan!
小声点
Quiet.
彼德
Peter!
彼德 你还好吧
Peter, are you okay?
- 没想到你那么厉害 - 你太酷了
- I can't believe you did that. - That was so cool.
- 换了我 腿都软了 - 太棒了
- You gave me chills. - It was great.
干得好
Nice work. Come on,
东西给我 走吧
give me the game. Let's go.
真倒霉
Oh, no.
装自然一点
Act natural.
把它藏起来
Hide the game.
每次有麻烦
Every time there's trouble,
都碰到你
I run into you.
我怎么 我不懂你的意思
Me? I don't know what you're talking about.
- 跟我到局里 - 哪也不去
- I'm taking you in. - I'm not going anywhere.
等一下 别带他走 他是...
Just a second. You can't take him, he's...
她的未婚夫
Her fianc?
他不是你姑丈吗
Wait a minute.You said he's your uncle.
没关系 我马上回来
It's all right. I'll be back soon.
混蛋
Blast!
你说不会背弃朋友
You said you'd never abandon your friends.
- 等会再玩 - 等会
- We'll finish the game later. - Later?
范培特在这里
Van Pelt. Van Pelt.
我奉劝你们即刻回家
I suggest you all go home now.
现在怎么玩得完
Now how are we supposed to finish the game?
没他就玩不成了
We can't. We can't finish it without him.
朱蒂
Judy!
恩
What?
怎么回事
What happened?
我想自己玩完 我只差十步
I thought I could end the game. I was only 10 spaces away.
"游戏规则 若有违背"
"A law of Jumanji hadn't been broken...
"略施薄惩 棋子退回"
...you will slip back more than your token."
你想作弊
You tried to cheat?
我把骰子轻轻放下 弄出十二点
No, I tried to drop the dice so they landed on 12.
那就是作弊了
Okay, honey. Well, that would be cheating.
彼德 你的手
Peter, your hands!
你看你的手
Look at your hands!
我是威利
Come in, this is Willy.
动物朝巴氏公园前进 我挡不了
They cleaned out Larry's Hardware.I can't stop them.
快请求军队支援
Get the National Guard down here.
这是怎么回事 我知道你清楚
What is this about? I know you know.
没错 但说了你也不相信 卡尔
Yes, I do. But you wouldn't believe me even if I told you, Carl.
你怎么知道我叫卡尔
Wait a minute. How do you know my name is Carl?
我知道的可多了
I know a lot more than that.
你以前在巴氏鞋厂工作
You used to work at Parrish Shoes.
大伙叫你"鞋底师"
They used to call you "Sole Man".
"鞋底师" 没错 我本来在那上班
Sole Man, that's right. I was in there too...
后来被开除了
...till old man Parrish fired me.
- 他把你炒了 - 是啊
- He fired you? - Yeah, man.
而我有样东西原本可挽救全镇
And I had something that could've turned this whole town around.
你设计的鞋
Your shoes.
对啊
Right.
卡尔...
Listen, Carl?
虽然说迟了26年
I know it doesn't mean much after 26 years...
但是 很抱歉
...but I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
什么对不起
Sorry for what?
我是艾伦
It's me. Alan.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么回事
What's going on?
显然是商店在打折
Well, apparently there's a sale, honey.
刚才骑车的是猴子吧
You saw three monkeys on a motorcycle, didn't you?
- 是的 - 看来我没疯
- Yes. - Good girl.
说不定能保他出来
Maybe we can bail him out with a cheque.
谢谢你
Thank you.
跟那个胆小鬼说...
Tell that snivelling coward if he wants...
滚开 滚开
Get out of my way!
给我
Give me that, boy!
救命
Help me!
拉我出去
Get me out of here!
- 没关系 - 彼德
- It's all right. - Oh, my God, Peter.
跟上
Come on.
在那里
There it is.
在这等我
Wait here.
逮到你了 姑娘
Gotcha, girlie.
艾伦知道你被抓就会来找你
When Alan hears of your predicament, he'll come.
他不知道我在这儿 这招没用 再见
He doesn't know I'm here. It won't work. Your plan's ruined.
- 别动 否则宰了你 - 明白
- Move and I'll blow your brains out! - Okay.
快叫警察
Call the cops!
- 这样他就知道了 - 高明
- That should do the trick. - Oh, yeah.
扫描售价
Price check!
(未卖出)
放了我 就能收拾局面
If you let me go, I can stop all this.
听来难以置信 但我没骗你
It's like "The Twilight Zone", but it's true.
拜托帮个忙
Please, you gotta help me on this.
我一定会后悔
I know I'm gonna regret this.
不要动
Just hold still.
好 你自由了
There, I let you go.
现在怎么办
Now what are we gonna do?
- 你留在这里 - 我的钥匙
- You're staying here. - My keys!
这是为了你好
It's for your own good.
- 我的手铐钥匙 - 实在对不起了
- My handcuff keys! - I have to do this!
- 艾伦 - 你将来会感谢我的
- Alan! - You'll thank me someday.
卡尔 紧急情况
Carl, code red.
一名女子 两名儿童在多省超市遭劫持
Hostage situation at Sir Sav-a-lot. A woman and two children.
嫌犯似乎是你先前所说的人
It sounds like the armed perpetrator in the pith helmet.
卡尔 请回答
Carl? Come in, Carl.
什么是"多省超市"
What's Sir Sav-a-lot?
- 是平价量贩店 - 过去过去
- It's a discount store. - Move over.
- 轻一点 - 就这样 就这样
- Wait. Gently, gently. - All right, all right.
别紧张 我会开车
Don't worry, I've done this before.
曾今有一次
Once.
救命啊
Help!
超市在哪里?
Where's Sir Sav-a-lot?
- 门罗路 榆树街口 - 在教堂旁边
- Monroe and Elm. - The Episcopal church.
现在改成汉堡店了
Not anymore. Now it's a Speedy Burger.
至少原本是的 不知还在不在
At least it was. I don't know what's left. People are going loopy.
朱蒂
Judy!
有人追来了
We got company.
没关系 是交通警察
It's all right. He'll back us up.
- 游戏到手了 - 我们快走
- Here's the game. - Get out of here.
臭老鼠
Rats!
关掉警笛 就是那个
Turn the siren off. Right there!
知道了
Okay, I got it.
闭嘴女人 要杀你早就杀了
Stop cringing, I could have shot you at any moment.
你为何不下手
Why didn't you?
骰子不是你掷的 我找艾伦
You didn't roll the dice, Alan did.
在那边
There it is, there it is.
踩煞车
Hit the brakes!
煞车...
我踩啦
Hit the brakes!
他应该快到了
He'll be here.
莎拉
Sarah!
- 你没事 - 恩
- Are you okay? - Yes.
彼德呢
Where's Peter?
我在这儿
I'm here.
太好了
Oh, great.
因此要记住 周遭环境 永远在你掌握之中
So remember, circumstances are never, ever out of your control.
第三卷结束
End of tape three.
布兰福特镇骚动的最新消息...
Update on the extraordinary events in Brantford, New Hampshire.
至少已有98人住院...
98 people have been hospitalized with symptoms...
症状包括发烧 出疹和突发癫痫
... ranging from inexplicable fevers and rashes to seizures.
地方当局疲于应付
Local resources are strained to the breaking point.
州卫生局呼吁民众 若有类似症状 请拨911
And state officials are now asking those with such symptoms to dial 911.
行了
I got it.
艾伦 安慰他一下
Alan, talk to him, please?
我哪有时间
What? We don't have time for this, okay?
他是个孩子 只是想帮忙
I know, but he's a kid and he was trying to help.
- 好吧 - 我带他谢谢你
- All right, come on. - Thank you.
朱蒂 来一下
Judy, come on.
我曾经警告过你
I warned you about this, Peter.
但你就是不听 还要玩
No, you wanted to play the game.
你在哭吗
What, are you crying?
别哭 不要气馁
You don't cry, you keep your chin up.
来 振作一点
Come on, keep your chin up.
哭永远解决不了问题
Crying never helped anybody do anything.
碰到问题
If you have a problem,
就要勇敢地面对
you face it like a man.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我在丛林待了26年
Twenty-six years buried in the deepest jungle...
仍然免不了像我父亲
...and I still became my father.
来 对不起
It's okay. Come here, I'm sorry.
没关系
Hey, it's all right.
你说过的 害怕也没关系
It's all right to be afraid.
我不是害怕
It's not that.
那是为什么
What is it?
准备好没
Ready?
别担心
Don't worry,
我们马上就把你变回原形
we'll have you back to your old self in no time flat.
我们这就进去
Because we'll go in here together,
坐下来 把游戏结束
sit down and finish that game.
不论发生...
No matter...
什么事
...what.
我好像真正回到了家
Suddenly, I feel right at home.
(车门未关)
洛莲 这是卡尔
Lorraine, this is Carl.
我知道问题所在 我要去巴氏旧宅 请派人支援
I'm heading over to the Parrish place. Give me some backup.
洛莲
Lorraine?
等一下
Wait! Wait!
又怎么了
Now what?
停车
Stop!
等一下
Wait! Stop!
有什么问题
Is there a problem?
能不能送我回家
Can I have a ride home?
- 你住哪里 - 杰弗逊街 巴氏旧宅
- Where do you live? - Jefferson Street. The old Parrish place.
你有没有小孩 一男一女
Do you have children? A boy and a girl?
发生什么事了
What happened?
上车 路上慢慢说
Get in. I'll explain it all on the way.
好嘛拿去算了
Fine! Take it!
快点去你家
We gotta get to that house.
去别处玩吧
Shouldn't we play someplace else?
不 我在这种环境长大 外头更恐怖
No.I grew up in this. It's out there that scares me.
该我了
Okay, it's my turn.
莎拉 掷个十二点 你就赢了
Sarah, if you roll a 12, you win.
准备好 要掷了
Okay, ready? Here I go.
没关系
It's okay.
"每月月逢二分圆"
"Every month at the quarter moon,
"大雨降临..."
there'll be a monsoon...
"浊浪滔天"
...in your lagoon."
大雨
Monsoon.
至少我们在屋里
At least we're inside.
可不是吗
Yeah, right.
下点雨也无妨
Well, a little rain never hurt anybody.
太多了淹死人
But a lot can kill you.
咱们走
Come on!
这边走
This way!
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
往高处走 别走散了
We get to higher ground. Come on! Stay together!
你没事吧
You okay?
- 艾伦 - 在
- Alan? - What?
那是什么
What is that?
妈呀 快闪
Swim! Swim! Look out!
快逃
Swim! Go! Move!
继续走
Keep going!
坐在桌上
Stay on the table!
脚离开水
Feet out of the water!
到吊灯上去
On the chandelier!
莎拉 来
Come on, Sarah.
坚持一下
Hang on, Sarah!
受伤没
Are you okay?
朱蒂 彼德
Judy? Peter!
小姐 交给我处理 可能没事
Step back and let me handle this, please.
可能电视的声音开大了点
It's nothing. They probably left the TV on too loud.
我就等这一天 小心了
I always wanted to do this. Could you step back, please?
手伸过来
Give me your hand!
抓住我的手
Grab my hand!
抓住了
I got it.
拿着
Take the game.
- 你没事吧 - 恩
- You okay? - Yeah.
你为了我 跟美洲鳄鱼搏斗
Alan, you wrestled an alligator for me.
是非洲鳄鱼
It was a crocodile.
美洲鳄鱼特征不一样
Alligators don't have that fringe on their hind leg.
来吧
Come on.
是我搞错了
My mistake.
来
Come on.
好 该我了
Okay, it's my turn.
我知道了
I've got it!
我们就像福尔摩斯
Colonel Mustard in the library with the wrench.
答案就在游戏中
Clue.
"注意你站的地方"
"Beware the ground on which you stand.
"地板不如你想象"
The floor is quicker than the sand."
救我
Help me.
保持冷静
Stay calm.
不要挣扎
Don't struggle.
- 保持冷静 - 我很冷静啊
- Stay calm. - I'm calm.
抓住
Grab on!
拉
Pull!
抓住了 拉
I got it. Pull!
冷静 冷静
Stay calm!
快点
Come on!
好极了
Oh, good!
就好了...
I got you...
别给我会散开的东西
Stop giving me things that come apart!
"有个教训..."
"There is a lesson..."
有了
All right.
"有个教训宜记取"
"There is lesson you will learn."
我抓住你了
I got you.
"有时得先退回去"
"Sometimes you must go back a turn."
你痛不痛
Did I hurt you?
不会
No.
谢谢你 朱蒂 你脑筋转得快
Thank you, Judy. Thank you. That was very quick thinking.
莎拉和我想要站起来
Sarah and I would like to get out of the floor.
彼德 该你掷了
It's your turn, Peter.
我以为又要失去你了
I thought I'd lost you again.
谢谢你没走开
Thanks for sticking around this time.
"需要人手别慌张"
"Need a hand ? Why you just wait
"七手八脚来帮忙"
We'll help you out. We each have eight."
什么东西
What's that? What is it?
- 没事 - 没事干嘛哇哇叫
- Nothing. - You don't go "Ah!" for nothing.
彼德 去院子工具间找把斧子 快去
Peter, my dad kept an axe in the woodshed. Go get it!
快去快回
Hurry! Go, go, go!
朱蒂
Judy?
彼德
Peter?
劳拉阿姨 是我 彼德
Aunt Nora, it's me. Peter.
对不起 我很忙 等会再解释
Sorry. I can't talk right now. I'll explain later.
- 莎拉 - 干嘛
- Sarah. - What?
该你了
It's your turn.
- 掷个七点 就结束了 - 我没办法掷 把骰子放在嘴里
- You can finish if you roll 7. - I can't roll.
- 把骰子放在嘴里 - 朱蒂 把游戏搬过来
- Put the dice in your mouth. - Judy bring the game. Hurry!
朱蒂
Judy!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事 去帮他们
I'm fine. Help them.
快来 朱蒂
Come on, Judy.
把骰子给我
Give me the dice.
"紧要关头目标近"
"You're almost there with much at stake.
"地牛翻身陷困境"
But now the ground begins to quake."
真希望爸妈在这里
I wish Mom and Dad were here.
我也是
So do I.
只有游戏结束 才活得成
Her only chance is if we finish the game!
现在该你
It's your turn!
妈妈呀
Oh, my God!
抓住游戏盒
Get the game!
我不要放开你
I won't let you go!
不许动
Don't move.
站起来
Stand up.
手里拿着什么
What's in your hand?
丢掉
Drop it.
没路走了 小伙子
End of the line, Sonny Jim.
游戏到此为止
Game's up.
赶紧跑路
Start running.
不
No.
你不怕
Aren't you afraid?
我怕死了
I'm terrified.
但我父亲说过
But my father told me...
你要面对害怕的事
...you should always face what you're afraid of.
好孩子
Good lad.
你终于成了男子汉
You're finally acting like a man.
有什么遗言
Any last words?
魔幻棋
Jumanji.
我说魔幻棋
It's Jumanji.
不
No, Alan, no!
我忘了带演讲稿
I forgot my speech notes.
我好高兴你回来了
Dad, I'm so glad you're back.
我才去了五分钟
I've only been gone 5 minutes.
我觉得好像很久
It seems like a lot longer to me.
不是说不跟我说话吗
I thought you were never going to talk to me again.
无论我说了什么 老爹
Whatever I said, Dad,
对不起
I'm sorry.
艾伦...
Look, Alan,
我刚才很生气
I was angry.
我也很抱歉 对不起
I'm sorry too, son.
听我说
Look,
如果你不想念克利福塞 我不勉强你
you don't have to go to Cliffside if you don't want to.
我们明天再谈
Let's talk it over tomorrow.
两个大男人
Man-to-man.
像父子好了
How about father to son?
好
Great.
我得走了 我是主客
I've gotta get going. I'm the guest of honour.
老爸
Dad
在196...
Back in 196...
我是说...
I mean...
今天在鞋厂的事
today in the factory...
不能怪卡尔·班特利
...it wasn't Carl Bentley's fault.
是我把鞋子放在生产线上
I put the shoe on the conveyer belt.
很高兴你告诉我
I'm glad you told me, son.
谢谢
Thanks.
再见 爸爸
Bye, Dad.
再见
Goodbye.
- 天哪朱蒂和彼德 - 艾伦
- Holy smokes! Judy and Peter! - Alan.
他们不在
They're not there.
现在是1969年
It's 1969.
他们还没出世呢
They don't even exist yet.
我快忘了当大人的滋味
I'm forgetting what it's like to be a grownup.
没关系
That's okay,
只要我们互相记得
as long as we don't forget each other.
还有朱蒂和彼德
Or Judy and Peter.
有件事我一直想做
There's something I've been wanting to do.
最好现在就做... 免得又像小孩什么都不敢
I better do it before I feel too much like a kid.
六年级不教开车吧
They probably don't teach driver training in the sixth grade, huh?
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
要不要尝尝
Do you want any cookies?
爸 是两用气垫式 销路好极了
Dad, the new cross-trainer's doing fabulous.
不是胸罩 是鞋子
No, it's not a bra, it's a shoe.
他们到了
Honey, they're here.
爸 我得挂了 圣诞快乐 明天来机场接你
Dad, I gotta run. We'll pick you up tomorrow, okay?
你们就是最好的礼物 拜拜
You'll be the best Christmas gift of all. Bye-bye!
他们到了 我们走
They're here? Come on, let's go.
借过 借过
Pardon me.
很高兴你们能来
Jim! Glad you could make it.
- 谢谢 这是我妻子 玛莎 - 这是莎拉
- Thanks. This is my wife, Martha. - Hi. This is Sarah.
- 你好莎拉 - 孩子呢?
- Hi, Sarah. - Where are the kids?
我的天来了
Oh, my God, there they are.
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
当然是猜的 孩子嘛
A guess, of course. They're your kids.
猜对了 他们正是
Right, these are our children.
朱蒂和彼德 见过巴先生 巴太太
Judy and Peter. Say hi to Mr. And Mrs. Parrish.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
跟我记忆中一摸一样
You're just like we remembered you.
我觉得跟他们很熟 因为...
I feel like we know so much about them.
- 你常跟艾伦谈起 - 我又跟内人说
- You've told Alan about them. - And I told her.
- 我去拿礼物 - 好 亲爱的
- I'll get the presents. - Sure, honey.
我们很喜欢小孩
Well, we love children.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
好棒
Cool
你哪天开始上班
When can you start?
我们想度假时去滑雪
We were going to take a skiing
去加拿大的洛矶山脉
holiday up in the Canadian Rockies.
别去
No!
对不起
Sorry.
我们在想...
We just...
新产品的广告得立刻开始
Need you to get that marketing done on the new line.
没问题 那就下周开始
No problem. I could start next week.
很好
Great.
我给你介绍几个未来的同事
Let me introduce you to the folks you'll be working with.
来吧
Come on in.
我家就是你家
Our house was your house.
随时欢迎
Is.Anytime you'd like.
那是什么声音
What's that sound?